Kevin Oversluizen

Rotterdam, South Holland, Netherlands



koversluizen@me.com



+31618526833



linkedin.com/in/kevin-oversluizen

Summary

Experienced eCommerce professional with a growing interest to branch out into a Front-end development job. Proven history of working in the fashion and the outdoor industry. Has a B.B.A. with a focus on Sportmarketing and Management from the Rotterdam University of Applied Sciences. Skilled in eCommerce, Merchandising (Demandware/SFCC), HTML, CSS, Google Analytics, Microsoft Office, Buying and Forecasting. Native in Dutch and full proffesional proficiency in English.

Experience



Online Merchandiser

Suitsupply

Sep 2021 - Present (10 months +)

Webshop Manager (Interim)

Garcia

Mar 2021 - Jul 2021 (5 months)

E-Commerce Merchandiser

KEEN

Jan 2020 - Mar 2021 (1 year 3 months)

- Work closely with internal teams to develop and execute site merchandising and content strategies to drive sales and conversion growth, support the product buy, and drive the Brand message.
- Recommend and execute seasonal promotional plans to maximize revenue and achieve gross margin targets.
- Drive sales, manage conversions, inventory turns & site optimization through the E-commerce platform (SalesForce Commerce Cloud).
- Responsible for on-site administration and setting up seasonal product offer (Digital catalogues, pricing and other digital assets).
- Actively work as a Content Coordinator with Digital Marketing and Design teams to provide images and content for web store and online promotions.
- Provide weekly reporting, analysis and insights on product performance for all categories and regions.
- Responsible for the KEEN Online Seasonal buy together with the Merchandise and Planner Manager.

E-Commerce Jr. Merchandiser

KEEN

Jan 2019 - Jan 2020 (1 year 1 month)

E-Commerce Assistant Merchandiser

KEEN

Dec 2017 - Jan 2019 (1 year 2 months)

Night Duty Manager

Mainport by Inntel Hotels Sep 2014 - Aug 2016 (2 years)

Night Duty Manager/ Security

QUSO

Nov 2012 - Sep 2014 (1 year 11 months)

Niveau 4 allround politiemedewerker (hoofdagent)

Politie Nederland

Jul 2010 - Oct 2012 (2 years 4 months)

Medewerker Callcentre

Stedin

Nov 2009 - Jun 2010 (8 months)

Education

Rotterdam University of Applied Sciences

Bachelor of Business Administration - BBA, CE: Sportmarketing en Management 2013 - 2017

🔊 국민대학교 (Kookmin University, Seoul)

Minor International Business, International Marketing and Business 2016 - 2017

Montessori Lyceum

HAVO diploma, Economie en maatschapij (management en organisatie erbij) 2003 - 2006

Libanon Lyceum

VMBO diploma, Natuur en gezondheid 1999 - 2003

Licenses & Certifications

HTML - W3Schools.com

CSS - W3Schools.com

1MLR0FL6V3

Skills

HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • GitHub • Online Merchandising • Salesforce Commerce Cloud (SFCC) • Microsoft Office • Data Analysis • English • Teamwork • Dutch